Welcome to the Summer Satellite Tutorial.
This tutorial is intended to help beginners understand the basic operations of Marvelous Designer.
Before starting, please download Marvelous Designer.
You can find the download method in the comments section.
After downloading the model, add the material material to the model.
Continue to download the hair line sticker.
Increase the strength of the hair line sticker.
We will make Marvelous Designer for Marvelous Designer.
Read the creation panel menu to find the tools.
Use the transverse tool to create the root of the leaf.
We will use it to create the leaf later.
We will create a side panel first, and then create a mirror-like panel.
Create a rectangular panel as the leaf part.
Add a fabric type.
Download the transverse material as the text of the new fabric.
Read the text tool menu.
Use the transverse text tool to select the transverse text to the appropriate size.
You can adjust the size of the panel according to your needs to match the reasonable leaf effect.
The right-hand corner positioning ball is used to move the text in various directions.
On the follow-up version, press the right button to select the order, and put it in front.
Use the tool and tool, and adjust it accordingly.
Use the tool to increase the straight line point and delete unnecessary points, so that the plate is as close to the outline as possible.
Use the tool and tool to adjust the outline of the plate to match the shape of the sticker.
You can move the straight line point to continue adjusting the plate.
Please note that when you move the straight line point, the curve will also be adjusted accordingly.
Continue adjusting the plate to the appropriate shape.
Please note that when you move the straight line point to the appropriate shape, the curve will also be adjusted accordingly.
As shown in the video, adjust the shape of the leaf plate to match the line point.
Please note that when you move the straight line point, the curve will also be adjusted accordingly.
Choose the gold paint, click Color Block, and dilute the color of the gold.
Change the name of the fabric to the appropriate name.
Change the name of the name of the fabric to the appropriate name.
Apply transparent paint to the leaf fabric.
We need to match the size and texture of the transparent paint.
Click the texture in the attribute editor, and change the width and height values to the corresponding attribute of the transparent paint.
We want to believe this effect.
We need to apply number 1 to tested needs to additionally
We could add points to Gibbum in approximately the whole height of the highest point length to an added point.
We can do the same with the bottom wire.
Use the multidirectional line tool to draw a line connecting the top point to the bottom point of the inner line.
If the inner line is not connected to the point when drawing, please use the edit sheet tool to manually move to the starting point of the creation.
Select the multidirectional line tool menu. Use the free multidirectional tool to select the multidirectional line for the leaf part first, and then draw an equivalent multidirectional line on the inner line.
Use the adjustment board tool to select the symmetrical board, board and multidirectional line on the leaf board and place the board in the right place.
Perform the same operation with the gold board.
Use the multidirectional line tool to merge the top of the board.
Move the leaf board to the side of the pine tree in order to prevent any insertion problems during simulation.
Then select the inner line of the gold board and press the right button to merge.
In the 3D window, press the right button to print.
Then use the multidirectional line tool to merge the left and right sides of the gold board.
The distance between the gold board and the look board is 80 mm.
In order to make the gold board, press the left button to print.
Press the left button to print with the left foot, and the left foot must not touch the gold board.
Select the multidirectional line tool to select the herself. Use the fixing pin to fix the gold board.
Add the fixing pin to the two sides of the gold board.
In the 3D window, drag the pin to the back of the board with the help of the fixing pin.
Drag the fixed pin to the back of the board like in the video.
Right-click on the fixed pin, select to delete all fixed pins and turn on the simulation.
Then, untangle the leaf board to harden them.
Turn on the simulation.
Move the leaf board to the right position.
We want to attach the leaf board to the green position of the top of the tree trunk.
Therefore, rotate the board to the right position.
Turn on the simulation after rotating to the appropriate position.
After the simulation is completed, use the fixed pin tool to add the fixed pin to the bottom grid of the root board.
When the simulation is started, use the fixed pin to drag the leaf board.
Copy and paste the leaf board and place the copied leaf board in the right position in both the 2D and 3D windows.
Place the leaf board before freezing.
When you have completed one leaf, repeat this step until all leaf boards are pasted on the tree trunk.
To better attach the fixed pin to the tree trunk, you can right-click on the fixed pin and select to attach the fixed pin to the virtual model.
Please refer to the video for the effect after completion.
After confirmation, please uninstall all boards.
Select the
Uninstall the simulation and start the simulation.
Now we can export the OBJ file.
Please confirm that you have selected the unified UV coordinates and the full shot and transparent image.
Now you can complete the simulation of the board and virtual model in the other 3D software that you often use.
Welcome to check out the tutorial of other summer atmosphere series and learn how to make other content in this scene.
Thank you for watching.